ROHIT PATIL

GRAPHIC DESIGNER & WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Mobile: (+91) 950-327-3800

Home Phone: (+91) 832-942-1827

Email address: rohhitpatil@gmail.com

Website: www.rohhitpatil1233.wixsite.com/mysite Address: AT- Khorochi, Tal - Indapur, Dist - Pune

Pine - 413114.

PROFILE

"I'm a graphic designer and native Pune currently living in Bangalore,

I love paper and books just as much as I love the internet and enjoy designing all types of projects across both print mediums and web."

Highly creative and multitalented Graphic Designer with extensive experience in multimedia, marketing, and print design. Exceptional collaborative and interpersonal skills; dynamic team player with well-developed written and verbal communication abilities.

RELATED EXPERIENCE

CONCEDGE COMMUNITCTION PVT LVT

Jr. Graphic Designer - 2016 to 2017

REXAWARE SOLUTION PVT LMT.

Graphic Designer & Web Developer - 2017 to 2018

TAGOS DESIGN INNOVATIONS PVT LMT

Sr. Graphic Designer

EDUCATIONAL ATTAINMENT

WALCHAND VIDYALAYA & JR COLLEGE KALAMB HSC (2012-13)

VIDYA PRATISHTHAN'S POLYTECHNIC COLLEGE

Computer Diploma (2013-15)

P. A. INAMDAR COLLEGE OF VISUAL EFFECTS, DESIGN & ART

Graphic and Web Design (2015-16)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

